Indiana University Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology records, 1942-2010 C383
Indiana University Archives
- Special Projects, 1944-2010 (Box 5)
  - Public Initiatives, 1967-2007 (Box 7)
    - Folklore and Education (Box 7)
      - 1994-1996 (Box 7)
      - Contacts, 1979-1994 (Box 7)
    - Folklore to You, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Going to School at Honey Creek: Suggestions for Teachers and Pupils, Monroe County Community School Corp., undated (Box 7)
    - Halloween (Box 7)
      - Proposal drafts, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
      - Grant application, interview transcripts, and release forms, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
      - Fieldwork and legend class proposals, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
    - Heritage Studies (Box 8)
      - Resource Center Catalog, Unionville School, undated (Box 8)
      - Resource Material, undated (Box 8)
      - Sharing Our Heritage: Using a Building as a Teaching Tool, Carol Darling, Monroe County Community Schools, undated (Box 8)
      - Teaching Materials, Monroe County Community School Corporation, Honey Creek School, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Microfilm (Box 13)
      - Groslier, Georges, Danseuses Cambodgiennes, Anciennes et modernes. (neg), undated (Box 13)
      - Knosp, Gaston, Rapport sur une Mission Officielle d'etude musicale en Indochine. (neg), undated (Box 13)
      - Marchal, Sappho, Danses Cambodgiennes (neg), undated (Box 13)
      - Materials on Laos nos. 1-20, undated (Box 13)
      - Societe des Etudes Chansons Cambodgiennes (neg), undated (Box 13)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities: Research Resources Proposal (Dorson), 1975-1980 (Box 8)
    - The Place Where We Live: Then and Now in Monroe County, Indiana, Monroe County Community School Corporation (Box 8)
      - Historic Tours of Bloomington, 1989 (Box 8)
      - A Guide for Teachers by Carol Darling and Maxine Dunfee, Monroe County Community School Corporation, Intro, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Data Sheets, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Interviews, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Maps, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Pictures, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Stories, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Projects, Tales Online [TOL] (Box 8)
      - 1997-2002 (Box 8)
      - Advisory Board, 2001-2002 (Box 8)
      - Analysts' Manual, undated (Box 8)
      - Class Projects, 2002 (Box 8)
      - Collections List, 2001 (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 8)
      - Gathering, Chicago, 16 February 2002, 2000-2002 (Box 18)
      - Indiana University Press, undated (Box 8)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 2001-2003 (Box 8)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 2002 (Box 8)
      - Screens, 2002 (Box 8)
      - Style Manual, undated (Box 8)
      - Teachers' Institutes, 2003 (Box 8)
      - Testing, 2003 (Box 8)
      - Thesaurus, 2000 (Box 8)
      - Users' Manual, undated (Box 8)
      - Workshop - Illinois, 2002 (Box 18)
      - An Electronic Database of Folklore Narrative, 2003 (Box 8)
      - Berea Folktale Workshop, 2003 (Box 8)
      - Projects Berea Folktale Workshop Applications, 2003 (Box 18)
      - Projects, Berea Folktale Workshop Photos, undated (Box 8)
      - Project, Berea Folktale Workshop Website, 2003-2004 (Box 8)
        Two floppy disks have been removed for preservation purposes. For more information, please contact Indiana University Archives staff.
    - Public Folklore Classes (Box 8)
      - F402/802, 2000 (Box 8)
      - F404/804 Indiana Folk Arts Survey, 1998 (Box 18)
      - F740 Folklore in the Public Sphere, 1998 (Box 18)
      - Public Folklore: Can Folklorists and Educators Work Together? RM Dorson, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Initiatives (Box 8)
      - Distance Learning (Dolby), 1997 (Box 8)
      - Women and Authority (Stoeltje) 1987, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
    - Public Folklore Initiatives (Box 8)
      - 1978-1989 (Box 8)
      - 1971-1997 and circa 1990s (Box 8)
      - 2000-2007 and circa 2000s (Box 8)
      - Activist Pedagogy, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
      - Activist Pedagogy, Common Ground Project, 1998-2002 (Box 8)
        One zip disk and one CD have been removed for preservation purposes. For more information, please contact Indiana University Archives staff.
      - American Folklore Society Interviews, 1989 (Box 18)
      - Great Lakes Arts Alliance, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
      - Indiana Arts Commission (IAC) Correspondence, 1980-1984 and circa 1980s (Box 9)
      - Indiana Arts Commission /NEH Proposals (unfunded), 1995-1997 and circa 1990s (Box 9)
      - Internship Models, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
      - MEDIA, 1978-2001 (Box 9)
      - Strategic Directions (IU) Not Funded (1996) (Box 9)
      - Traditional Arts Indiana, Midwestern Folklore, 2009 (Box 9)
      - Traditional Arts Indiana, Update newsletter, 1989-1993 (Box 9)
    - Public Folklore Initiatives: Field School (Box 9)
      - 1990s-2000s (Box 9)
      - Carpenter Class Presentations African Studies, Empathy/Field School, 2000 (Box 9)
      - Models, 1994-1999 (Box 9)
      - Publications, circa 2002 (Box 9)
      - Publicity, 1994-2000 (Box 9)
    - Public Folklore Initiative: Field School: Disabilities 2001 (Box 9)
      - Announcements and Initiatives, 2001 (Box 9)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 9)
      - Curriculum, 2001 (Box 9)
      - Evaluation, 2001 (Box 9)
      - Logistics, 2000-2001 (Box 9)
      - Materials, 2001 (Box 9)
      - Notes, 2001 (Box 9)
      - Participants, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Public Folklore Initiative: Field School: Disability and Community, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Public Folklore Initiatives: Field School: Town Square (Box 9)
      - Announcements, 1999-2000 (Box 9)
      - Applications, 2000 (Box 18)
      - Budgets, 2000 (Box 9)
      - Curriculum, 2000 (Box 9)
      - Logistics, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Public Folklore Initiatives: Residency (American Folklore Society/ IU) (Box 9)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 9)
      - Residency Material, 1994 (Box 18)
      - Planning Notes, undated (Box 9)
      - Program: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 9)
      - Public Sector Residency Application, 1994-1995 (Box 18)
      - Public Sector Residency – Applications – requests for app. Forms, 1994-1995 (Box 18)
      - Public Folklore Residency Guidelines, 1992 (Box 9)
      - Riki, Saltzman, 1995 (Box 18)
      - Residency: People who applied, 1993-94 (Box 18)
      - Public Folklore Residency Reports, 1993 (Box 9)
      - Spitzer, Nick, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
      - Amy Skillman, 1993 (Box 18)
      - Program, DeNatale, Gail Matthews, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    - Public Practice (Box 9)
      - Classes F803, 1996 (Box 9)
      - Classes F497 Capstone, 2003 (Box 18)
      - F404 Disability, 2001 (Box 9)
      - Planning Committee, 2000-2005 (Box 9)
      - Presentations, 2001-2004 (Box 9)
      - Presentations: F501, 1993-1999 (Box 9)
      - Service-Learning, 1996-2000 (Box 9)
    - School of Education Connections, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Simmon's Folklore Bibliography (Box 9)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 9)
      - Correspondence Biblio, 1967-1995 (Box 9)
      - Ishi, 1975-1978 (Box 9)
    - Simon Bronner/Penn State: "Cultural Diversity and Folk Traditions in Education" Conference, 1994 (Box 9)
    - U-matic (Box 13)
      - Ellen, Mrs. Richardson 1, undated (Box 13)
      - Exteriors – Moving 1, undated (Box 13)
      - Helen Arthur 1, undated (Box 13)
      - Helen Arthur 2, undated (Box 13)
      - Helen Arthur 3, undated (Box 13)
      - Noel I, undated (Box 13)
      - Noel II, undated (Box 13)
      - Noel III, undated (Box 13)
      - Noel IV, undated (Box 13)
      - Noel V, undated (Box 13)
      - Outside – Clear Creek Farm…Gospel Tab Store From 16th St., undated (Box 13)
      - Richardson – Mrs. Ellen and Ellen, undated (Box 13)
      - Steve Richardson, undated (Box 13)
      - Tiller 1 Interview, undated (Box 13)
      - Tiller 2, undated (Box 13)
      - Tiller 3, undated (Box 13)
  - Grants and Budget Information, 1975-2005 (Box 9)
    - A Type-Index for Tales of the Arab World – El-Shamy, September 1, 1985-August, 31, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Agreement Forms: "Identity Preservation Through Traditionalizing", 1984 (Box 9)
    - Archive Statement of Account, March 1, 1982 - April 29, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Archives Personnel, Folklore Institute Grant Department, 1981-1984 (Box 19)
    - Archives of Traditional Music (ATM) (Box 9)
      - March 9, 2005 (Box 9)
      - Grant Request 6/04 #9, 2004-2005 (Box 9)
    - Conference: The Future of American Folklife, Participants, October 12-14, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence Archive, 1979-1982 (Box 10)
    - Encyclopedia of American Folklife Proposal, 1975-1980 (Box 10)
    - Folklore Institute Grants, Special Projects Reports, 1977-1990 (Box 10)
    - Fund for Folk Culture Projects, 1997-1999 (Box 10)
    - Grant Records, 1978-1982 (Box 10)
    - Indianapolis Grant: Not Funded, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Journal of Folklore Research, Old Statements, 2001-2005 (Box 10)
    - Main Library Grant Proposal Folklore, 1982 (Box 10)
    - McDowell – Summer Seminar NEH [National Endowment for the Humanities], 1984 (Box 10)
    - Monographs – Statements of Accounts, October 1979-1981 (Box 10)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 10)
      - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Division of Research Grants, Dr. Harold C. Cannon, November 22, 1978 (Box 10)
      - Grant: Preservation and Access, June 2002 – July 2004 (Box 10)
        One CD has been removed for preservation purposes. For more information, please contact Indiana University Archives staff.
      - Seminar - Progress sheet on request for papers, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Special Programs: "Assisting Community Projects" Programs, 1980-1982 (Box 10)
      - NEH [National Endowment for the Humanities] Summer Seminar, 1976-1978 (Box 10)
      - Summer Seminar Proposal for 1979, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
    - New Grant Proposals, 2005 (Box 10)
    - Old Statements, Monograph (Box 10)
      - 1980-2005 (Box 10)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 10)
    - Smithsonian Grant, American Regions, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Conferences and Colloquia, 1979-2017
    - Conferences: National Women's Studies Association, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Edinburgh Folk Narrative Research Conference, Trip Dorson, July 1979 (Box 10)
    - Conferences: Ethnography of American Folklife, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - Ethnography of American Folklife Conference, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Tapes Transcriptions, American Folklife Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - American Folklore Society Meeting, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Folk Medicine Symposium, 1979-1984 (Box 10)
    - Folk Medicine, Indiana Council on the Humanities, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Conference: Assessment Folklore (unrealized), 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Conferences Kalevala, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
      Original negatives moved to Archives Photograph Collection
    - Swann Jones, Steven, October 1984-October 1985 (Box 10)
    - Journal of Folklore Research Comparative Method Abstracts, undated (Box 10)
    - Dundes, Alan, April-October 1985 (Box 10)
    - Honko, Lauri, April-August 1985 (Box 10)
    - Hasan-Rokem, Galit, May-September 1985 (Box 10)
    - Ben-Amos, Dan, August 1985 (Box 10)
    - Austerlitz, Robert, Cancelled, June 13, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Georges, Robert, June-August 1985 (Box 10)
    - Publicity, June-September 1985 (Box 10)
    - To Do Notes Kalevala, June-September 1985 (Box 10)
    - Abstracts, July 1985 (Box 10)
    - Bayerle, Gustav, July 1985 (Box 10)
    - Hufford, David J., July-September 1985 (Box 10)
    - Nenola-Kallio, Aili, July-September 1985 (Box 10)
    - Wilson, William A., July-August 1985 (Box 10)
    - Final Report, National Endowment for the Humanities, August 1985 (Box 10)
    - Goldberg, Christine, August 26, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Pentikäinen, Juha, August 26, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Flight Information, September 1985 (Box 10)
    - Conference Programs, F-A, September 1985 (Box 10)
    - Kalevala: Packet for Conference Participants, September 1985 (Box 10)
    - Apo, Satu, September 4, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Siikala, Anna Leena, October 1985 (Box 10)
    - Conferences Kalevala (Dégh), 1985 (Box 10)
    - Finnish-American Proposal: National Endowment for the Humanities, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Guest Lists, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Kalevala, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 10)
    - The Kalevala, The Comparative Method and Beyond: A Symposium of American and Finnish Folklore, September 1985; (12 audiocassettes) (Box 13)
      Digital Versions Available
      Digitized copies are available for these recordings. Please contact University Archives staff for access.
      - 1 (Bodner, Dégh, Georges, Honko, Dundes), September 26, 1985 (Box 13)
        Introduction to the symposium; Presentations by Dr. John Bodner (introductory remarks), Dr. Linda Dégh (on rethinking the historic-geographic method), Dr. Lauri Honko (on intellectual underpinnings of the Finnish method), Dr. Robert Georges (on types of comparisons of forms and variations), Dr. Alan Dundes ("The Anthropologist and the Comparative Method in Folklore").
      - 2 (Discussion), September 26, 1985 (Box 13)
        Discussion featuring Dr. Juha Pentikäinen, Dr. David Hufford, Dr. Galit Hasan-Rokem, Dr. Robert Georges, Dr. Felix Oinas, Dr. Hasan El-Shamy, Dr. Anna Leena Siikala, Dr. Alan Dundes, Dr. Dan Ben-Amos, Dr. Linda Dégh, and Dr. Steven Swann Jones on controversies in using the Finnish Method and tale-types.
      - 3 (Roberts, El-Shamy, Goldberg, Swann Jones), September 26, 1985 (Box 13)
        Presentations by Dr. Warren Roberts (on Stith Thompson and the motif-index), Dr. Hasan El-Shamy ("From Historic-Geographic to Historic-Demographic: An Evaluation of the Finnish Method"), Dr. Christine Goldberg ("The Architecture of Folktales"), and Dr. Steven Swann Jones ("Structural and Thematic Applications of the Comparative Method").
      - 4 (Swann Jones, Discussion), September 26, 1985 (Box 13)
        Conclusion of Dr. Steven Swann Jones's presentation; Discussion featuring Dr. Lauri Honko, Dr. Steven Swann Jones, Dr. David Hufford, Dr. Galit Hasan-Rokem, Dr. Alan Dundes, Dr. Hasan El-Shamy, Dr. Dan Ben-Amos, and Dr. Robert Georges on meaning and symbolism in motifs.
      - 5 (Thompson Hays, Various Speakers), September 26, 1985 (Box 13)
        Presentation by Marguerite Thompson Hays on the life and work of Stith Thompson, followed by brief reflections by Dr. Warren Roberts, Dr. Dan Ben-Amos, and Dr. Juha Pentikäinen.
      - 6 (Various Speakers, Oinas, Sudjanen), September 26, 1985 (Box 13)
        Conclusion of Marguerite Thompson Hays' presentation; Presentations by Dr. Felix Oinas ("Folk and National Epics of Finland and Estonia") and Dr. Sudjanen ("The Kalevala in Fnnish Vocal Music").
      - 7 (Nenola-Kallio, Siikala, Discussion), September 27, 1985 (Box 13)
        Conclusion of Dr. Sudjanen's presentation; Presentations by Dr. Aili Nenola-Kallio ("Units of Comparison in the Study of Baltic Finnish Laments") and Dr. Anna Leena Siikala ("Variation in the Incantation and Mythical Thinking"); Discussion featuring Dr. Felix Oinas, Dr. Anna Leena Siikala, Dr. Warren Roberts, Dr. Juha Pentikäinen, Dr. Nenola-Kallio, and Dr. Linda Dégh on sorcery and shamanism, lament and incantation traditions, performance and questions of worldview, modernity, and mythical thinking.
      - 8 (Hufford, Virtanen, Pentikäinen), September 27, 1985 (Box 13)
        Discussion featuring Dr. David Hufford, Dr. Felix Oinas, Dr. Warren Roberts, Dr. Hasan El-Shamy, and Dr. Alan Dundes on keening and lamenting traditions, folk and national epics, worldview, and translation concerns; Presentations by Dr. David Hufford (on supernatural belief, sleep paralysis and the comparitive method), Dr. Virtanen ("Is there a folk of the city?"), and Dr. Juha Pentikäinen (on the Kalevala, shamanism, rune singing and runic poetry).
      - 9 (Wiggins, Discussion), September 27, 1985 (Box 13)
        Conclusion of Dr. Juha Pentikäinen's presentation; Presentation by Dr. William H. Wiggins (on Emancipation celebrations and Juneteenth); Discussion featuring Dr. Hasan El-Shamy, Dr. David Hufford, Dr. Linda Dégh, Dr. Lauri Honko, Dr. Dan Ben-Amos, Dr. Galit Hasan-Rokem, Dr. Alan Dundes, Dr. Anna Leena Siikala, Dr. Juha Pentikäinen, Dr. Steven Swanna Jones, and Dr. Virtanen on experience-orientated research, motifs, parallels, and psychology in sleep paralysis accounts.
      - 10 (Apo, Hasan-Rokem), September 28, 1985 (Box 13)
        Presentations by Dr. Virtanen (introductory remarks), Dr. Satu Apo (on the study of folktales in Finland and Scandinavia) and Dr. Galit Hasan-Rokem ("A Semiotic View of Type and Oikotype"); Discussion featuring Dr. Warren Roberts, Dr. Linda Dégh, Dr. Satu Apo, Dr. Felix Oinas, Dr. Virtanen, Dr. Juha Pentikäinen, Dr. Alan Dundes, Dr. Lauri Honko, Dr. Dan Ben-Amos, and Dr. Galit Hasan-Rokem on concerns with archiving folklore and accounting for change in oikotypes.
      - 11 (Ben-Amos, Discussion), September 28, 1985 (Box 13)
        Presentation by Dr. Dan Ben-Amos (on reformulating the Finnish Method and folk narrative); Discussion featuring Dr. Virtanen, Dr. Linda Dégh, Dr. Lauri Honko, Dr. Dan Ben-Amos, Dr. David Hufford, Dr. Galit Hasan-Rokem, Dr. Felix Oinas, Dr. Anna Leena Siikala, Dr. Steven Swann Jones, Dr. Hasan El-Shamy, Dr. Juha Pentikäinen, and Dr. Alan Dundes on generic categories, comparison, non-tradtional narratives, meaning, text and context, performance, nationalism and internationalism, archives, and the future and responsibility of the field.
      - 12 (Concluding Discussion), September 28, 1985 (Box 13)
        Conclusion of the discussion and the symposium featuring Dr. Dan Ben-Amos, Dr. Linda Dégh, Dr. Lauri Honko, and Dr. Juha Pentikäinen on text and context, internationalism, and publications in the Journal of Folklore Research.
    - Folklorists in 1984: A Survey, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
    - C. B. Cultural Basics Conference Brochure and Program, 1988-1992 (Box 13)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
    - Conference: Women: Peace and Authority, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
    - Conferences: Folksong (Cohen) 1991, 1989-1995 (Box 11)
    - Letter Liaison: Re Conference Information, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Conference Bureau, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Conference – Letters (samples), October 1991-June 1992 (Box 11)
    - Conference Planning Meeting Records, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Conferences (Proposed) Mass Demonstrations as Rituals of Dissent, 1991-92 (Box 11)
    - Freetown Village, January 1992 (Box 11)
    - Conference Budget, January-February 1992 (Box 11)
    - Cultural Basics News Releases, February-May 1992 (Box 11)
    - Conference Food and Lodging Space Arrangements, May-June 1992 (Box 11)
    - AV List final for conference, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Focus Session I Media: Spitzer and Pentikäinen, 1992 (Box 11)
    - American Folklore Society (AFS) Program Committee Correspondence, June 3, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Charles Briggs, Plenary #1 (Thurs), July 1992 (Box 11)
    - Plenary #2 Organized by John Roberts, May-September 1992 (Box 11)
    - Plenary #3 Barb Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, September 1992 (Box 11)
    - For Prelim Program – From local arrangements, June 1992 (Box 11)
    - Preliminary Program (Printers copy without codes), 1992 (Box 11)
    - Preliminary Program: with room numbers and lists with panel numbers, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Special Events, Requests and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Video File: Abstracts and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11)
    - 1992 Committee Report (Box 11)
    - Draft of Final Program, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Cultural Basics Publication, September-October 1992 (Box 11)
    - Conferences: Cultural Basics (Hamer), 1992 (Box 19)
    - Cultural Basics (Box 11)
      - Publicity Efforts, 1992 (Box 11)
      - Conference Speakers and People Invited, 1992 (Box 11)
      - Participation and Organization of Small Groups, 1992 (Box 11)
      - Sample Materials from Book Display, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Folklore and Education Bibliographies, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Folklore Colloquium, 1993 (Box 11)
    - Colloquia: Post-Soviet Folklore Defns, 1994 (Box 11)
    - American Folklore Society and Society for Ethnomusicology (First Time Together) Milwaukee, Wisconsin, October 1994 (Box 11)
    - American Folklore Society Meeting, Lafayette, Louisiana, October 1, 1995 (Box 11)
    - Conference: Folklore and English Departments 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Folklore in the Academy, May 20, 1995; (9 audiocassettes) (Box 13)
    - Colloquium Series, 1996 (Box 11)
    - Conferences (proposed) Summer Institute, 1996-1999 (Box 11)
    - Conferences: Myth Symposium, 1997-1999 (Box 11)
    - Public Folklore Initiative: Putting Theory to Work Conference, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Myth: A Symposium Conference (Box 11)
      - Preparation Notes, 1998 (Box 11)
      - Notes, 1998-1999 (Box 11)
      - Conference Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 11)
      - Manuscript, 1998-1999 (Box 11)
        Four floppy disks have been removed for preservation purposes. For more information, please contact Indiana University Archives staff.
      - Book proposal updates, May 1999 (Box 11)
    - Myth: A New Symposium (Box 11)
      - Revisions, January 2001 (Box 11)
      - General, 2001 (Box 11)
      - Manuscripts and Notes, 2001 (Box 12)
      - Manuscript IU Press sent to referees, undated (Box 12)
      - R.D. Fulk, Myth in Historical Perspective: The Case of Pagan Deities in the Anglo-Saxon Royal Genealogies, undated (Box 12)
      - Schriempp and Hansen, Myth, undated (Box 12)
    - 50th Anniversary Conference, 2002-2003 (Box 12)
    - Words and Things and Music: Modes of Cultural Production, 2003 (Box 12)
    - First Annual Indiana University Folklore and Ethnomusicology Symposium, December 2006 (Box 12)
    - Conference on the Future of American Folkloristics, 2017 (Box 12)